<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nate&#39;s Place</title>
    <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nate&#39;s Place</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 11:26:59 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sozi</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/sozi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 11:26:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/sozi/</guid>
      <description>So what is Sozi? Sozi is the name of a software program which allows us to make make an SVG (scaleable vector graphic) into an animated slideshow via HTML.
Today I want to spend very short amount of time to see if I can embed a Sozi built presentation into this blog post.
Here goes! First: Create an SVG.   This SVG image was created with Inkscape.   Second: Open the SVG in Sozi and make a slideshow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 09:01:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Though our family has a website, its main purpose is not as a blog but as a newsletter and prayer list. I also set up another website this past week for our church here in Japan, Siloam Intl. Christian church&amp;ndash;in Japanese, of course. Both sites are Github Pages and were built with Hugo using the Ananke theme. Through the experience of getting these two sites set up, I found that I really enjoyed writing the updates and that I am always tempted to write too much and off subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nematomorpha</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/nematomorpha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 13:50:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/nematomorpha/</guid>
      <description>Remember the movie “Alien”? I still remember watching it as a kid at a friend’s house and being really, really scared. I think the most frightening thing about it was simply the thought of having a large parasite living inside of one’s gut. Or perhaps it was the idea of that parasite one day deciding to make its way out. Thankfully, besides the occasional tapeworm, human beings do not have to deal with very large creatures living inside of (or forcing their way out of) our bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Workers Are Few</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/the-workers-are-few/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:07:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/natesplace/blog/the-workers-are-few/</guid>
      <description>Content wise, this is similar to this post on our family site. But I wanted to make a simple appeal for those of you who love the Lord Jesus and want to see the light of the gospel shine more brightly in Japan.
Japan, with a population of about 127 million people, has a seemingly insignificant number of fellowshipping, growing disciples of Christ. The Japanese people are considered one of the largest unreached people groups in the world and are desperately in need prayer and of workers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>